Good morning.
It's been a while.
I got a receipt for the delivery.
I'm going to the store.
Good morning.
I'm checking my clothes.
I put my jacket on top of my clothes
today.
What is it?
This top is the point.
This is a knitwear, but it's oversized.
If you take it out, you can wear it like
a dress.
I don't usually use colors like this.
I think this is cute sometimes.
I was a little cold when I took it out.
I brought tights, so I'll wear them when
I get home.
This is a gift.
It's an undercover.
I like it.
I'm going to the store.
Good morning.
I'll put it on.
What's this?
It's a self-made jacket.
No! I really don't like it!
I haven't been very particular about my
clothes lately.
I'm not interested in clothes.
I'll show you what I have.
First, I have this.
I'm wearing a knit shirt.
I'm wearing a comfortable one.
And I'm wearing my younger brother's
jacket.
I'm wearing a knit shirt and a headband.
I'm wearing a jacket.
That's it.
I love Chinese clothes.
I brought some clothes for my YouTube
channel.
I have two bags.
I brought this.
I have one with ini clothes
Maybe I was getting lazy
when checking the clothes last time.
They looked new.
My clothes weren'tأ
I need vintage confidence.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, too.
Here's Kira-chan!
I'm Nukiuchi!
I'm in a good place!
You're in a good place!
Sorry, I suddenly...
No, no, no, no.
My clothes were quite boring.
Is that all?
Yes, that's all.
Please.
So cute!
You're so cute, Kira-chan!
Yes.
Nukiuchi's clothes are like this.
Cute!
Today's point is this.
It's a unique point.
What?
The clothes are designed differently.
What else?
What's inside?
I'm wearing this white vest.
Oh, cute.
And I'm wearing a blazer today.
It's stylish.
How about you, Yuz?
I'm done.
What?
Yuz, you already talked.
Do you want to hear it?
I haven't heard it.
No, it's fine!
I can just watch it.
I think I'm cute.
I'm going to bed.
Good morning.
I'm checking my clothes.
What's that pose?
It's totally different.
Well, the color.
It's been a while.
I've been wearing jeans a lot lately.
I'm wearing a color-coded outfit today.
This pink top is from JETTY.
This is from NAMANO.
This is a coat.
This coat and skirt are from APE.
That's it.
I'm done.
Go back to your seat.
I'm tired.
The point is the clothes on top.
You mean the clothes I wear often?
Yes.
I'm wearing cargo pants and warm
trainers.
I'm wearing warm clothes.
Simple is the best.
I think the point is that the shoes are
colored.
I don't know if it's right.
Blue.
Are you carrying a bag today?
I didn't carry it last time.
I see.
What's in it?
My wallet and...
I took off my rubber bag.
Oh, really?
That's all.
Good morning.
Are you turning?
I'm turning.
Good morning.
It's been a while.
I was with two people the other day.
I'm nervous about being alone.
What's the point?
Today, I'm wearing a tie.
I'm wearing a tie.
I'm wearing a lot of things.
Tie, inner, shirt, and cardigan.
I've seen the colors.
And this is...
This is a bag that Minami gave me as a
birthday present.
I love it.
I bought this at BEAMS.
This cardigan is a collaboration between
Atmos Pink and Girls Girls.
This is the old one of Burberry.
This is a vintage of Real Papa.
These are Dr. Martin's shoes.
These are their shoes.
Good morning.
He's Aquaman!
Yes.
I'm checking my clothes.
I thought so.
It's getting warmer.
Spring is coming.
I chose sporty clothes.
This is from a Korean brand called
KODOGRAPHY.
This is my sister's.
I forgot this.
I'm into matcha tea latte lately.
I got a rare receipt today.
Really.
I ordered it.
It's only matcha tea latte, but it's
been so long.
I answered this survey and it says it's
free for tall sizes.
I heard it doesn't come out much.
Tall size drinks are free of charge.
I was told it was an illusion receipt.
Please wait a minute.
No.
I want this.
Look at this.
I've never seen this before.
I read this and answered it.
I got this number.
Let's go.
I'm saying this.
It's just one.
I'll drink this now.
I got this today.
I'm lucky.
I will do my best today.
I'm going to the gym.
Good morning.
What is it?
It's a check-up check.
The second check-up check.
The point of today is that I want to get
a new shiny belt from my fans.
I put on a pink leg warmer and a star-
shaped one.
I made it a little brighter.
This is Shaggy.
Shaggy, Shaggy, Shaggy.
This is also Shaggy.
This is long boots from Eblis.
This is Shimamura?
I think so. I bought it at Shimamura.
It's Y2K.
Did you enjoy the clothes of all the
members?
Please try to imitate or wear it.
Bye bye.